## Kai Jun Tey, Software Developer

 $Notting ham, United\ Kingdom, 07825788123, teykaijun 123@gmail.com$ 

LINKS	Portfolio, LinkedIn			
PROFILE	Computer Science with Artificial Intelligence graduate from the University of Nottingham and a freelance software developer, with a long-term career goal of becoming a professional developer. I am proficient in C#, Python and have experience in software designing, developing, machine learnings combined with soft skills sucl as time management, critical thinking, and socialling skills.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Jun 2021 — Sep 2022	Unity VR Developer, Dr Khoo Teng Jin			
	<ul> <li>Created a mobile app using Unity that displays chemical molecules in a 3D environment for students to study chemical molecule's structure in a 3D view.</li> <li>Made a VR game for research in gamification in education.</li> </ul>			
Aug 2019 — Aug 2020	University Open Day Guide, University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus			
	<ul> <li>Responsible for guiding and explaining information and features of the university to visitors who visits the university</li> </ul>			
Sep 2021 — Aug 2022	Waiter, Hot 9 Restaurant			
	<ul> <li>Worked as a part time waiter at a hotpot restaurant near University of Nottingham Jubilee Campus.</li> <li>Responsible for engaging and serving customers.</li> <li>Gained experience in aspects of managing a restaurant</li> </ul>			
EDUCATION				
Jan 2013 — Dec 2017	High School, Kuen Cheng High School			
	<ul> <li>Graduated with an A-level equivalent exam result</li> <li>That has A's in Maths, English, Bio, Physics, and Chemistry</li> </ul>			
Apr 2018 — Aug 2022	Bachelor's in Computer Science with AI, University of Nottingham			
	• Graduated with 2:1 clas	s.	,	
SKILLS	Unity Engine	Experienced	Machine Learning	Skillful
	C#	Experienced	Computer Vision	Beginner
	Python	Skillful	Front-End Development	Skillful
	Game Development	Experienced	Back-End Development	Skillful
	Data Science	Skillful	VR / AR Development	Skillful

## EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Jan 2016 — Dec 2017 Team Leader, Lion Dance Club

- Responsible in conducting training sessions
- Leading the team on outdoor activities and performance

Jan 2020 — Dec 2022 Event Chairman, 24 Festive Drum

 $\bullet \quad \text{Managed a 24 Festive Drum Concert held at the University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus.} \\$